{"Topic": "Mouth and its Parts", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "What is the number of deciduous teeth in human beings?", "op1": "20", "op2": "16", "op3": "22", "op4": "14", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Tongue is attached to the floor of the mouth by \u2013", "op1": "sublingual papilla", "op2": "uvula", "op3": "lingual frenum", "op4": "labial frenum", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Mandible is the other name for which of the following parts?", "op1": "upper jaw", "op2": "lower jaw", "op3": "tongue", "op4": "gums", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which are the largest salivary glands?", "op1": "Parotid", "op2": "Sublingual", "op3": "Submandibular", "op4": "All are of same size", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which of these enzymes is present in saliva?", "op1": "Pepsin", "op2": "Trypsin", "op3": "Maltase", "op4": "Lysozyme", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following is also known as the maxilla?", "op1": "lower jaw", "op2": "upper jaw", "op3": "tonsils", "op4": "lips", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which type of teeth are used to grind food?", "op1": "Molars", "op2": "Incisors", "op3": "Canines", "op4": "Premolars", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which of the following prevents the food from going into the nose?", "op1": "tonsils", "op2": "gingival", "op3": "Uvula", "op4": "tongue", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which of the following prevents the food from entering the trachea?", "op1": "Frenum", "op2": "Papilla", "op3": "Uvula Epiglottis", "op4": "Epiglottis", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": ". How many wisdom teeth does an adult generally have?", "op1": "2", "op2": "4", "op3": "6", "op4": "8", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": ". The oral cavity is also known as the \u2013", "op1": "Buccal cavity", "op2": "cranial cavity", "op3": "thoracic cavity", "op4": "pleural cavity", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": ". The total number of molars in the mouth of a human being is \u2013", "op1": "Six", "op2": "Eight", "op3": "Ten", "op4": "Twelve", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": ". The function of the enzyme lysozyme is \u2013", "op1": "to kill bacteria", "op2": "to digest carbohydrate", "op3": "to digest protein", "op4": "to digest fat", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": ". Genioglossus is a muscle found in the \u2013", "op1": "cheeks", "op2": "lower jaw", "op3": "tongue", "op4": "throat", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": ". What is the number of premolars in the mouth?", "op1": "12", "op2": "8", "op3": "10", "op4": "6", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": ". Which type of teeth is also known as cuspid?", "op1": "Canine", "op2": "Incisor", "op3": "Premolar", "op4": "Molar", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": ". Which tonsils are visible through the open mouth?", "op1": "Lingual", "op2": "Pharyngeal", "op3": "Adenoid", "op4": "Palatine", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": ". Function of which of the following is to kill germs and help to prevent throat and lung infections?", "op1": "Uvula", "op2": "Palate", "op3": "Tonsils", "op4": "Tongue", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": ". Which of the following diseases is not related to mouth?", "op1": "Gingivitis", "op2": "Halitosis", "op3": "Thrush", "op4": "Gout", "Answer": 3}]}